yobongo.com 2012-12-25

# Yobongo - Chat with people nearby - About

### This Privacy Policy describes Yobongoâ€™s policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. Yobongo receives your information through our various mobile apps, web sites, services and third-parties ("Services"). When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Yobongo in the United States or any other country where Yobongo operates. If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@yobongo.com.](mailto:privacy@yobongo.com)

## Information Collection and Use

### Information Collected Upon Registration: When you create or reconfigure a Yobongo account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, password, phone number, photo, and email address. Some of this information, for example, your name and photo, is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results.

### Additional Information: You may provide us with additional information to make public, such as a short biography. You may customize your account with information such as a cell phone number for the delivery of SMS messages or your address book so that we can help you find Yobongo users you know. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on our web site. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional.

### Yobongo Messages: Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information with the people around you and the world. Most of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to make public. This includes not only the messages you send and the metadata provided with messages, such as when you sent the message. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide public. You should be careful about all information that will be made public by Yobongo, not just your messages.

### Yobongo Private Messages: Private messages you send to others are just that, private. We will not share or view your private messages. They are safe and secure.

### Location Information: We do not share you specific location information publicly. However, we do use your location information to connect you with others on Yobongo.

### Log Data: Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data. Links: Yobongo may keep track of how you interact with links in messages across our Services including third party clients by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, including advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

### Cookies: Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at public user profiles or lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Yobongo may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

### Third Party Services: Yobongo uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP request.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Your Consent: We may share or disclose your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your Yobongo account.

### Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to obligations mirroring the protections of this privacy policy.

### Law and Harm: We may disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Yobongo's rights or property.

### Business Transfers: In the event that Yobongo is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

### Non-Private or Non-Personal Information: We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public Tweets or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did).

## Modifying Your Personal Information

### If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

## Our Policy Towards Children

### Our Services are not directed to people under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at [privacy@yobongo.com.](mailto:privacy@yobongo.com). We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.

## Changes to this Policy

### We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at <http://yobongo.com/privacy>. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we may notify you via e-mail to the email associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

### This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 3 2011.

### Thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy? Please, let us know.
